import {
  ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
  HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
  LessonsContentDictType
} from './SharedVariables'

const THIS_LESSONS_CONTENT: LessonsContentDictType = {
  'が-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'が',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'ga',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'が',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ga',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぎ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぎ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'gi',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぎ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'gi',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぐ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぐ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'gu',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぐ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'gu',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'げ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'げ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'ge',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'げ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ge',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ご-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ご',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'go',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ご',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'go',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ざ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ざ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'za',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ざ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'za',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'じ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'じ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'ji',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'じ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ji',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ず-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ず',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'zu',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ず',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'zu',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぜ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぜ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'ze',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぜ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ze',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぞ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぞ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'zo',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぞ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'zo',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'だ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'だ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'da',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'だ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'da',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぢ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぢ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'di',
      extraInfoList: [
        {
          header: 'Pronunciation Tip',
          explanation: 'Pronounced the same as じ'
        }
      ]
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぢ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'di',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'づ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'づ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'du',
      extraInfoList: [
        {
          header: 'Pronunciation Tip',
          explanation: 'Pronounced the same as ず'
        }
      ]
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'づ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'du',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'で-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'で',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'de',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'で',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'de',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ど-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ど',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'do',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ど',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'do',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ば-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ば',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'ba',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ば',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ba',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'び-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'び',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'bi',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'び',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'bi',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぶ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぶ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'bu',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぶ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'bu',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'べ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'べ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'be',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'べ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'be',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぼ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぼ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'bo',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぼ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'bo',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぱ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぱ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'pa',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぱ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'pa',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぴ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぴ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'pi',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぴ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'pi',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぷ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぷ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'pu',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぷ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'pu',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぺ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぺ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'pe',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぺ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'pe',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  'ぽ-ひらがな': {
    conceptType: HIRAGANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ぽ',
      explanationHeader: 'Romaji',
      explanation: 'po',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: ROMAJI_QUESTION_PROMPT,
        question: 'ぽ',
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false,
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'po',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}

export default THIS_LESSONS_CONTENT
